how can you make a course that can make
over a million dollar I want to answer
that for you here today my name is
Jeremiah Kowski and if I haven't met you
yet I've been working in the coaching
information publishing digital marketing
space for the last 21 years I built
multiple companies to over $10 million a
year and I help people that are
beginners as well as those that are just
starting how to make and scale
businesses to 10 20 and $30,000 per
month with coaching programs memberships
as well as online courses what I want to
break down for you is the process of
being able to create something that can
make you a sustainable income of over a
million but let's break it down simply
okay for you to make a million dollars
you got to make 10,000 20,000 30,000 duh
obviously what do you have a value that
you can actually offer that would be a
million dollars well the truth is if you
can take what you know that somebody
else
desires and you can teach it to other
people you can make money with that one
of the biggest things that I notic that
a lot of people deal with is they don't
have confidence that they have enough to
be able to make money with a course or a
program or or a training like that and
honestly it's because we're too caught
up in judging ourselves as well as
judging all this stuff that's out there
comparing ourselves to everybody else
that's out there realize that if you can
look at the info that you know and the
transformation that you can bring people
you can charge money for it so the
number one thing that I recommend is
pick a topic that you feel confident
about something that you have experience
in something that you have done before
and there's a variety of different ways
to pick topics like that you can even
use AI to help you brainstorm certain
topics to be able to use but the way
that I like to sell in a business that
actually makes seven figures is this
let's break down the numbers on this is
that if you have a course that is
$100 okay it's a decent price for a
course how many of these would you have
to sell to make a million dollar well
let's see how many zeros there are
one
three 4 okay so you would need to sell
at least
10,000 courses at
$100 to be able to make a million dollar
all right that would be $10,000 people
to pay you $100 but here's where the
math gets
interesting is that if you sell a course
or a program for
,000 the math changes completely you
only need a th000
people to buy that course to make a
million dollars if you sell a course for
$2500 how many do you need to sell to be
able to make a million dollars well you
only need to actually sell 400 and
that's really the math that we're
looking for is the multiples that create
economies at scale that you don't need
tens of thousands of people buying it to
be able to create that in reality people
that make millions of dollars don't do
so with $100 products they may have a
$100 product that's an entry-level
product but they end up having something
that's about ,000 to $2500 to be able to
sell to people and make the kind of
money that they want to make okay now
what is the process that we go out there
to be able to sell to people well you
can do that a variety of different ways
through social media through advertising
through going on podcasts blogging
reaching people people on the internet
and that's one of the number one things
that I Mentor people with in my
accelerator program is once they create
their course how do we sell it how do we
get clients how do we get leads how do
we get people to actually buy the thing
that we are that we've put our time and
effort and Blood Sweat and Tears into
okay and so the process of making a
million dollars with this is you figure
out number
one what is the transformation
that I can bring to somebody what is the
result that is
monetizable that I can charge and I
really want you to start thinking in
these numbers at least $2500 for okay
and here's why because if you're not
charging at least that much it's very
difficult to be able to kind of create
the kind of income that you want to make
and I meet a lot of people that come up
with a thousand and one reasons why they
won't let's split this number in half
let's just say say again you're selling
it for
$1,250 in today's economy everything is
worth that much if the value is there
and you can make sure that you can
deliver that value to People by showing
up with confidence by learning how to
structure it by how to put stuff
together and how to lead people to get
the result that they are looking for
okay and so what you want to do is you
want to pick a topic that people desire
so we have the transformation that you
can deliver you have the desire of the
prospect that they want you have the
thing that they want the most and when
you can package and connect these two
together and bridge the gap this creates
finances for you okay so you take your
experience the transformation you can
deliver to somebody and you start
teaching it to other people teaching it
over video teaching it in a program that
you sell to people an information
program and there's a process for
putting that together it's actually a
lot easier than most people think
there's very simple software used to be
super complicated years ago now it's so
simple cost effective and easy that I
think anybody can make 10,000 20,000 or
$30,000 a month doing this and then if
you want to go on to make a million
dollars you absolutely can as well and
that's exactly what I love helping
people with is is how to actually take
what do they know put it together in a
way that people want to buy put it
together in a way that people are that
people will say okay
how do I get more of that so what you
have to figure out though is the desire
that the person has the only way that
you're going to be able to sell
something is not with
information
information is a dime a dozen we have
YouTube right here you're watching this
on
YouTube information's
everywhere but the difference is
transformation and transformation comes
when people get into an environment with
you where they are making an investment
with you so they're putting their money
where their mouth is and they're taking
action with you to do something 99% of
the time people who just watch YouTube
videos don't get the results that they
are looking for until they make an
investment to get mentored by a coach or
by a trainer or by a mentor who can walk
them through those processes and so what
you do is you end up embodying the
mentor that they need the person that
can provide them with the results that
they are looking for that they are
seeking out so we're go far beyond
information and we go directly into the
transformation of how their life is
going to change and that becomes
directly connected to the desire that
they have once we understand those
things okay and there's a again there's
a process for understanding those
things we then go
into finding the people that we want to
reach we figure out where do they
congregate where do they spend their
most time where do they put their
attention and then you end up actively
promoting your course you tell people
about it this is something that people
end up doing way too passively they get
so passive they hope that people will
just end up finding them and then buying
the thing that they put out there when
the truth is that doesn't happen in
reality that you have to be actively
putting yourself out there not just
expecting people to find you because
you're awesome and I get that maybe you
are awesome but learn to promote and
that's where your money is going to come
from and then you got to actually close
the sale you have to know how to ask the
buying questions and how to get people
to make a purchase with you and this is
all built around people trusting you
people believing in the fact that you
can deliver on the thing that you say
that you are able to deliver on and so
one of the biggest mistakes that people
make is they're so focused on the what
that they're going to deliver they're so
focused on how they're going to help
people they're so focused on the the the
the
nitty-gritty indepth areas of well we're
going to do this and they end up
investing all of their time
into all the details when they're not
paying attention to who are the people
that are out there that we're going to
promote to and this is where you want to
put your focus you want to put your
focus on these people that are right
here what do they want what do they
desire and how can we bring bring them
into your space and into your ecosystem
and so the number one thing that you
have to
do is you have to grow your email list
and you have to get people onto an email
list and and and into a community with
you to where you can
connect with them based on those desires
that they have okay and so when you're
able to connect with people based on the
desires that they have you're able to
lead them to to the result that you can
deliver it takes active leadership too
many people are so passive in this
process where they're working on how do
I look right to people and how do I
master the marketing side of things and
and so focus on perfectionism doing all
the things perfectly posturing
themselves how do I appear like somebody
that people can trust when in
reality it just boils down to learning
how to how to how to use the words that
you say and the words that you write in
a way that actually makes a real
tangible connection with people when you
can connect with people and they trust
you so you connect with them you can
never build trust with somebody unless
there is a
connection there is enough people and
things and stuff out there that is
trying to get people's attention that's
trying to connect so we go from
attention to connection
to trust
okay and I can look at even in the in
the dating world that's exactly what we
do we got attention you get the
attention of a of a of a mate connection
you actually start to like each other
and then trust is built and then that's
where
commitment comes from and getting
commitment out of people both in what
they're going to do for themselves and
that's is where the purchase comes from
so these four stages of capturing
attention getting people to see
you and being willing to be
seen is the first stage of it one of the
biggest reasons why most people never
grow in their business is they're trying
to not get attention from people they
don't want attention they don't want
people to see or notice
them and then on the flip side they wish
that people would see the value that
they have to offer but they don't want
too much
attention or maybe they do want
attention but they don't actually want
connection they just want it for selfish
reasons of what they
desire neither of those is going to
build trust with anybody because people
see right through that and they don't
want anything to do with people that
that appear or look like they have
ulterior motives overall and that's how
you look when you're not doing this
effectively when you're not learning how
to communicate and connect with people
in the way that truly truly
matters and when you can't build trust
you're never going to get the commitment
of people actually purchasing something
from you actually choosing to work with
you actually choosing to take that next
step with you not passively not just oh
wow that's some good information oh wow
like here's my email address but then
they're gone to tomorrow but like an
actual tangible they're going to make an
investment with you where they're going
to spend money with you and by doing
that not only are they going to spend
money with you but they are committed to
the result that you end up promising
people so the idea is you end up
attracting the right people to you when
you can connect with the right people to
gain their trust and build that
commitment so the goal is that you don't
want to attract
unqualified buyers and this is one of
the biggest mistakes that people make is
that they're hoping that everybody out
there sees them or whatever it is and
and and I just wish that somebody would
notice me out there when the truth is
not everybody is qualified for the thing
that you're going to be offering them
you want to find people that are
actually qualified for the things that
you are selling for what is in your
course so again if you're still bent out
of shape
wondering what should I put in my course
that would have a value to people that
they would want to buy it I want you to
literally like stop overthinking about
that if I can just encourage you on one
thing and and like when we like step out
of that that we're worried is it going
to be good enough am I going to are
people going to like it are they going
to be disappointed in me if I get it
wrong that worry and fear that fear of
missing out all of this fear is the
Kryptonite to this whole process when
you're operating out of fear you can't
make connection you can't build trust
and you're not going to get people's
attention or Garner commitment or
financial results okay so fear really is
the killer of your business overall when
you're operating in fear you're not
operating in your best you're not
showing up as your best you're letting
your emotions get the best of you
instead of focusing in on how can I make
that connection with somebody and this
is where a lot of the people that I meet
are is that they're really really
focused on I want to make money I want
to build a business but I'm just so
afraid of doing it wrong or picking the
wrong thing or going the wrong path
about this when you got to let go of
that and you got to let go of allowing
fear worry insecurity to stop you
business involves taking risk now we
don't want to take inordinate risk at
all we don't want to be
Reckless but we have to learn how to put
ourselves out there to be able to get
attention create connection build trust
and then create commitment in people so
that they make a purchase with us and so
that starts by understanding
[Applause]
what is it that your Target customer
actually wants what do they want more
than anything else to be able to get the
attention of your Target customer you
have to understand their deepest desires
you have to understand what are they
afraid of that they don't want to happen
what are their fears what are their
worries what are their doubts what are
their insecurities and then you connect
that to the transformation that you can
deliver and then what you end up putting
into your course you end up putting into
your program is the thing that they
desired the most and the process of
getting there the process of reaching
that goal we have courses in my coaching
program that are all about how to put
this together and how to create a course
that is world class that delivers
results to people in your marketing and
this is where we kind of split these two
things together is we do have the
delivery side of things this is where
you're actually um teaching and actually
delivering the content this is where you
teach this is where you Mentor this is
the results that are
delivered what you have to do in your
marketing side of things because you can
do all of this right here and I know
people that do they're excellent at this
and they're broke and they're not making
any money and they're not getting any
clients no matter how amazing this
is we think that this is going to turn
into cash flow and it's not true it
doesn't all it does is it leaves us with
a headache if that's all we're focused
on now it's great and it's important to
deliver results to people but if you're
not marketing and actively connecting
with people and selling and reaching
people you're never going to have people
that you can actually deliver any kind
of results to overall in a course or a
program or a coaching program okay so we
have to learn how to Market and how to
sell to people and this is where we
connect with we tap right into the
result that we're going to deliver we
end up owning that result we end up
owning the outcome and communicating
that with people and we end up leading
with the desire as well as the fantasy
that people really want what do they
fantasize about the most what do they
wish was the reality for them what do
they wish they could experience more
than anything else okay so you package
this up in some form of content that you
can deliver to people you got to make
some kind of a Content that you require
people to either pay you for a lowcost
value or you give for free could be in
the form of a 15minute video could be a
90minut video could be a 30-minute video
could be a YouTube video like this this
is an example of sales and marketing
done
well it's exactly that is when you can
deliver content that has value to people
and they can show up to listen to it it
starts to build that trust it starts to
build that connection and then it gives
you an opportunity to present people
with how you're able to deliver that
result in transformation that is
directly connected to the desire and the
fantasy that people have for the outcome
okay so then we work backwards from
there is we can build out marketing
materials for this we can create
advertising campaigns we can create
landing pages and opt-in forms we can
create offers that connect with people
and get them to buy into the thing that
we are offering them one of the biggest
mistakes that I notic that most coaches
and mentors make is they're great at
coaching and they stink at marketing and
sales and they don't know how to
actually connect and communicate with
people that gets people to make a buying
decision they're purely focused on
delivering these results which is again
it's great it's awesome but it's not
going to make you any money if that's
all your focused on you got to learn how
to Market and how to communicate in a
way that actually gets people to buy
from you that actually gets people to
say okay I'm ready to make a change in
my life and you start to bring that
transformation and you start to shape
the minds and the thoughts of people to
start moving in the direction of the
thing that you have to offer so this
takes boldness this takes confidence
this takes you showing up fully
believing in the thing that you're
putting out there
and then being willing to attract a lot
of people in front of
you and we like to use things such as
video content that people can sign up
for for free we use live events that
people can sign up for and then from
there that gives us the opportunity to
build
trust to
connect and to present what we have for
sale so you have to have some kind of a
mechanism video training that's going to
connect with people build trust and
present the thing that we're asking them
to make commitment with okay so all of
that has to fit together and so if you
let's say you don't have you're like I
don't have the skill in being able to
create video content or I don't feel
confident on camera things like that
okay I understand maybe you love
connecting with people you got to deal
with what are we afraid of what are we
trying to avoid what do we think is
going to happen if we get on camera and
start to learn that it's actually going
to be the best vehicle in your life to
be able to build your business and to
get the clients that you want to have
and that that insecurity that you might
be feeling if you
do is is only temporary and that you can
learn to get comfortable with what might
feel uncomfortable one of the number one
strategies that you have to be able to
do if you're going to be able to be
successful as a business owner is get
comfortable with what feels
uncomfortable and what maybe you're like
I I don't feel the best at doing this as
far as that it goes when it comes to
your sales and
marketing it's one of those things that
I tell people you just you have to learn
how to get comfortable with selling and
with marketing and with reaching people
and so then when you do that and you can
and you can start to learn how to calm
your nervous system down and you start
to hear your inner voice and you focus
more on connecting with people and less
on what do they think about me CU really
the reason why we feel uncomfortable is
we're so focused on what does everybody
think about me what do I feel we're very
inner focused so we can start to move
more outer focused to where other people
are at with what are they experiencing
with what are they feeling and how can I
make that connection with somebody it
allows us an opportunity to start to
Market and sell the stuff that we have
to offer to people okay so that happens
by getting in front of people with with
some form of video content some kind
where you get them to actually watch the
content where they're actually going to
spend time with you and consume that
content why would people want to spend
time with you to consume the content
that you put out there because it's
connected with promising what they
desire and the outcome so you got to
learn how to make bold promises for what
you're able to deliver to people and it
has to be directly connected to the
desire that the person has and so in
your sales and marketing you end up
boldly promising the thing that they
want the most now is everybody going to
believe you no that's not reality but
the ones that really resonate with you
and there's mechanisms to build trust
with people with this most people are
going to be skeptical of coaches and
mentors that's just how it is in the
world today okay so more so than ever
you got to learn how to demonstrate that
value you got to be able to show people
that you know your stuff and that you're
somebody that they should listen to and
they're somebody that they should engage
with and that you're somebody that they
can truly truly spend time with and that
they want to spend time with in your
ecosystem one of the biggest things is
that when you build one of these
businesses
successfully is that people will want to
spend more time with you when you start
to embody this type of energy so one of
the biggest mistakes again that people
make is that they're so timid they're so
afraid they're so worried we're so stuck
up in logic and and and and and caught
up in our
feelings and when we can learn to just
kind of let go of all those
things and start to just enjoy the
process and have fun and start to be
more playful more often and start to do
more fun I'm telling you one of the
biggest strategies I get my coaching
clients is that if they're struggling in
their business is to go do something
that's fun if you haven't in a while and
stop focusing so much on all the stuff
you got to get done perfectly in your
business stop focusing on all the stuff
that you got to make sure is right and
put together perfectly as far as that
goes and start to just truly believe
that you have a message that people want
that you're going to show up that's
excellent and people have a desire to
spend time and listen to you now it can
be hard and it can be frustrating if
you've been doing this for a long time
and you're not getting results and you
don't have people buying from you and
maybe you're doing all the right things
and you've taken all the courses and all
the trainings and it's not producing the
results that you want the reason why
that I've noticed is that often times
it's because We're looping inside of our
own thoughts and we think that we're
doing all the right things when in fact
we're we're showing up in a way that's
repelling the right people and nobody is
actually being drawn in or attracted to
the things that we're doing so when we
can learn to communicate in a way that
is attractive to the right
people that draws them into our space
that draws them into our
ecosystem that makes them want to spend
more time with us that makes them want
to dive deeper into the concepts that we
have and you learn how to communicate
with the words and the language that you
say and how you show
up and you can learn how to trigger
positive emotions in how you communicate
and you can learn to teach in an
engaging way and you can learn to Market
in an engaging way where it doesn't feel
like people are consuming sales or
marketing material but you're actually
delivering value to people that my
friends makes the greatest return on
your investment overall in your business
and again that's one of the number one
things that I get to help people with
every single week inside my client
growth accelerator programs people come
to me they got coaching programs they
got courses and they're wondering how do
I get clients how do I make people
become a customer of mine and they're
struggling right where you're at and I
walk them through our process and our
system for doing this and I teach them
the nuances of how to do this and we
dive deep into what is the psychology
what are the systems and then how to
keep it simple that's number one one of
the best most important things is
keeping it simple if we overwhelm
ourselves overall with trying to do all
these things we end up doing nothing and
that's what I see happen with a lot of
people that struggle and fail is that
they're trying to do so much and they're
spread themselves so thin trying to be
perfect to try to make it work or they
think they need to do so much that they
don't do anything at all because they're
stuck and they're worried and they're so
insecure about getting it wrong or
making a mistake I usually see people on
both sides of the
spectrum and what I encourage is
literally like just let go of all that
pressure just release it just start to
have more fun start to relax go spend
time with one of your best friends with
your spouse go watch a movie go read a
book that you like go watch a TV show go
go you know go work out something to get
the body in in the blood flowing go for
a walk somewhere to get out of your
head to get out of your
feelings to get out of the
stuckness so then you can show up with
power and with excitement and with
enthusiasm and then that attracts the
right people to
you and then when you can do that and
you make that an extension of the result
that you deliver to people we really got
to get so like we're so caught up with
making sure that everything works and
that we're doing all the right things so
often just give it your best
shot just do your best
relax and have fun with
it and then learn the systems and the
processes of marketing building a lead
magnet building a landing page building
out a
funnel how do you then once people are
in your funnel how do you sell to those
people and that's exactly what we go
through and Mentor people on in my
coaching program the client growth
accelerator is how do we once we make a
connection with people once we really
truly connect with people how do we take
it a step further to be able to lead
people to a sale you can't do it
passively anymore my friends you can't
do it with what well I got so much value
they just got to see it I'm sorry you
got to be active and actually putting
yourself out there making a connection
with
people because all your competitors
right now are doing all of that and
more and the game has changed in the
last 5 years to where you have to learn
how to truly connect with people in
order to get clients and and maybe
you're good at doing that one on one to
one or oneon-one with people but at
scale
when you can do that in a group setting
or you can sell a course to multiple
people you got to learn how to make the
same level of connection that you do
with people oneon-one
at scale in a group and there's
mechanisms for doing that and video
content is the number one best way to be
able to do that at scale because I can
teach one message right now that then
can reach many many people at one time I
can send an email out to five th000
10,000 100,000 people to reach them with
the message and offer that we have and
then from there we're able to take them
on a journey with us to be able to build
that connection build that trust and
invite them to make a commitment for
their life and their future and to work
with us to get the results that they
want and so when you can learn how to do
this and you can learn anybody can learn
how to do this is exactly I Mentor
people on every single week in my
coaching program you can make money in
your business this is what most people
don't know how to do this is what most
course creators and coaches don't know
how to do is they're so just
like so focused on the information and
what do I deliver and what is my Niche
and all of that when it takes learning
to put yourself out there and connect
with people truly make a
connection to then get them to make that
commitment to buy from you okay I'd love
for you to make a commitment to work
with me and to join my coaching program
the client growth accelerator program
I'd love to see you in there we I I just
I enjoy working with people from all
walks of life from all different
backgrounds helping them get
results I've been doing this for 21
years and I can help you get results as
well jump in there I'd love to have you
we'll talk soon have a good one